[{"answer": "And they sent you out here to be posted", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You want to see the frontier", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm wondering sir, how will I be getting there", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No sir, it's just that I don't know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How far do you make the fort", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How far", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So things bein' the way they are we might as well turn around and get started back", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "This is my... are you crazy boy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well... I'll let 'em know where you are", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good luck lieutenant", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Buffalo", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Buffalo", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Buffalo", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Buffalo", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I want you to try and remember the the word", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't want to know", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Buffalo...  Buffalo", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes. Buffalo", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Kicking", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Kicking Bird...  What does he... is he a chief", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "They are my friend enemies", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I asked that he would think about my going", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Dances With Wolves... that's right.  How do you say it", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Dances With Wolves", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He learns well... he is fast", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I do not understand", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Crying for who", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh... good... thank you... goodbye..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You would think they could have made a baby by now", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't think they're having a hard time", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's good to be out", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "We are trying for a baby", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "We are trying for a baby", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No waiting", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Dances-with-Wolves.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "There are no orders and there is no journal", "qsentId": 38}]